We're in middle school now. It's time to grow up. How long do you plan on reading these childish stories? Enough is enough.
Akira, you better not have bought any more manga. I haven't. Really? Well, good. I'd be worried if you're still watching anime. Well, I don't.
Hey, does someone want this? It came with the drink that I bought. Is that some anime thing? I don't know it. Neither do I. I've never seen it before.
Oh, that's the secret one, right? Seriously? Yeah. It's insane that you managed to pull it in one shot. You're so lucky. I don't know much about it, but that's awesome. It's mega rare.
I'm going now, princess.
Oh
Next are sausages.
All right, got them.
So then, just mint taiko and cheese.
Okay.
Look at the time.
Do you think my sister and the others are at the studio by now?
We now turn back the clock.
What? Juju doesn't cosplay anything except Magical Girls?
Yes. A while ago, she said she wanted to do other cosplays.
But she's scared she'd ruin the character's images because she's too short.
But I think my sister would look awesome in anything!
I know, right? She's stunning!
The thing is, I wasn't able to cosplay without my sister helping me out.
She's way more knowledgeable about it than I am.
So I'm not sure hearing it from me would be all that convincing.
It's all good. It's fine.
We can sort through whatever it is you're worried about.
So, let's have Juju cosplay Black Lobelia!
Huh? You have her outfit from the theatrical version, right?
What? You mean the ridiculously cute one?
I never ended up wearing it, though.
I sized down based on the reviews and it totally didn't fit.
Girl, I've been there before!
And we already have the wig in contact!
So if we pay for the studio, we'll be able to see Juju as Black Lobelia for free!
Sounds like it, yeah!
Oh, everyone! I'm so hyped!
Big Sis!
Huh?
Do you really think she'll show up to cosplay with us?
Here's an idea.
How about we invite her along for our location hunt this Saturday?
Then we reveal that we actually wanted to surprise her with a costume!
Look at you, big brain!
Back when we surprised Rana for her birthday, she was super happy about it!
Happy birthday!
Surprising her is a sure-fire win!
You really think so?
I bet Juju's gonna be hella stoked!
Why wasn't I told?!
Also, you shouldn't assume that everyone wants to be subject to surprises!
We're so sorry!
Black Lobelia from Blaze is my absolute favorite!
That's the reason I gave up on this!
I refuse to cosplay her!
Excuse me.
Wait!
Juju!
The reason you won't cosplay her!
According to Shinju, it's because of your height, but-
It's also because you're flat and babyface!
Wha-
But hey!
Turns out, I can help you deal with all of that!
Juju?
If you really want to try cosplaying her, you should just go for it!
There's no risk in trying, and if it doesn't work out, then you'll know for sure!
You may look better than you think if you actually give it a chance!
And if you don't like it, we can apologize to Shinju and Marin about it, okay?
It's on us for moving this along without asking you anyway.
I just got so excited when I saw all your cosplay photos, that I didn't think about your feelings.
That's normal for you.
I really am sorry about all this.
Yeah, me too.
I'm sorry.
How?
Huh?
How did you figure it out?
The reason why I refuse to do certain cosplays?
Oh, well, I just had a hunch that you and I might be in the same boat on this.
But my battle's not with a babyface.
Well, if I don't like it, then I'm going home.
So I guess you live in a Hina doll shop then, Gojo?
Yeah.
That's cool.
Oh, right.
Should we let your family know we're working here?
I'll try not to make too big of a mess.
He's not around today, but he knows that we're here.
Gotcha.
I've never seen tools like this before.
Do you make the dolls as well, Wakuna?
Well, I'm still in training.
So is the tip of this brush really supposed to be this thin?
It's called a kegaki brush.
And yeah, it's meant to be that fine.
We trim the bristles ourselves so that we can paint the really small details on the dolls.
I see.
That's neat.
I guess you have to draw on their little faces.
You couldn't paint something so intricate without years of experience.
It's gratifying when something you've been doing for a long time actually takes shape like this.
Right.
Let's get to work.
This petticoat is so adorable.
Right?
You want to look cute even where people can't see.
So let's start with a silicone bra, okay?
Don't worry.
It's brand new.
Hold up your boobs as much as possible and face the hook towards your belly button.
Yeah, perfect.
We also have a corset, so you'll be good to go.
It feel okay?
Yeah.
It's just, I've never had cleavage before is all.
So I'm happy.
I feel you girl.
I'm a double A cup, so it's not a big deal when I cosplay as guys.
But this is the trick I use to make them look way bigger.
I've tried a ton of methods, but this one works best, IMO.
The plan is to tape your face and eyelids to add more white to your eyes.
You okay with Hanapuri nose inserts?
They're fine.
I'll start with your wig cap first, so let's gather up your hair.
Okay.
I think it's totally fine not to want to cosplay a character who has a different body type than you.
But at the end of the day, most of us look vastly different from the characters we want to cosplay.
That actually bugged me a lot in the past.
My favorite character is Tsukasa Rindo.
He's almost 190 centimeters, so he's tall for a high schooler, and he's super hot and has really defined features.
But I'm kind of the exact opposite to all of that.
My face is plain and I'm 30 centimeters shorter.
Oh, I'm not bashing myself, it's just a fact.
When I cosplayed Tsukasa for the first time, I was totally in shock.
It was basically just me parading around in his tracksuit.
I saw just how much it didn't suit me and it really forced me to face reality.
I wanted to tell him, I'm sorry that someone like me tried to cosplay you, and I got super depressed.
But even so, I really loved him. I loved him so much that I didn't know how to handle it.
This might sound kind of weird, but I actually felt bad for cosplaying Tsukasa while I was depressed, if you can believe it.
To find the joy in cosplaying him again, I accepted that there are things I can't change.
I started to find ways to make myself look closer to Tsukasa in my photos, and make up for our differences.
You always looked awesome as him, Mia, even at the start!
Thank you, but I wasn't satisfied with it!
Miyako, when exactly did you start cosplaying?
Hmm, around my first or second year of middle school. Ten years or so.
Ten years...
Yeah, time's really flown by quickly.
Now, ready for makeup?
I'll be showing you all the techniques I learned through years of cosplaying Tsukasa.
So get ready to learn!
I never even considered reusing contacts for prop making.
Your detail work is amazing, they look surreal. No kidding.
Huh? Uh, wow, thank you very much!
You know, this is actually my first time making props holy from scratch like this.
Before this, we just used to use the next one.
I'm sure I've made a lot of puzzles.
I've never even considered reusing contacts for prop making.
Your detail work is amazing, they look surreal. No kidding.
Huh? Uh, wow, thank you very much!
You know, this is actually my first time making props holy from scratch like this.
Before this, we just used to use props for prop making this.
Wow, thank you very much!
You know, this is actually my first time
making props holy from scratch like this.
Before this, we just used pre-made horns and wings
for costumes.
You can make horns too.
Huh?
Seriously?
Yeah.
They take a lot of work, but they are fun to make.
So there were even more things I could have made
from scratch for her cosplays.
I wish I'd made them back then.
I'd like to try.
I'd like to make more props like this.
Yeah, you should.
If you're interested in it, you should give it a shot.
Right.
Now, we use the spatula to even it all out.
That'll do it.
We can finish once they're dry.
I can't believe they look so real.
You're such a pro.
How long have you been making props?
Not that long at all.
Suzuka and Miyako introduced me into this world
a community college, and I've been living in it ever since.
Sounds like fate.
They were short a person for a cosplay group,
so they roped me into it.
I would love to see a photo.
Do you have one?
I have a photo from the group we did this year.
President Luna!
Wait a second, is that you?
Yep.
I thought it would be a one-time thing for me,
but they kept asking me to cosplay with them.
Before I knew it, I was designing and building all our props.
It's weird, huh?
I wasn't even interested in cosplay before we met.
If you weren't interested, why did you keep going along with it?
Just once.
Whoa.
Hey, Yokota.
They're in my seminar.
My life is...
I had no idea you liked Blaze, too!
Of course she likes Blaze!
Everybody likes Blaze!
I love that they released Gacha for the movie!
Black Clobelly is always cute, but that fit is next level!
We need to cosplay against Stat!
I want to see you cosplay a girl this time!
To be honest, I didn't think anything good would ever happen to me.
But after meeting those two in college, I realized I'm as worthy as anyone.
I don't have to lie and pretend to be someone I'm not.
That's why, if there's ever anything I can do for those girls that'll bring them joy,
I'm going to do it.
So I cosplay.
Simple as that.
Totes late!
Sorry!
We brought ingredients for taco, yeah?
Shinju...
Miyako did my makeup.
Be honest.
What...
What do you think?
Does it suit me?
Personally, I'm not convinced.
It's like she walked out of the screen!
Perfect!
You look exactly like her!
I was right!
My big sis looks great in everything!
I've never really cared what other people think.
Is this how she felt?
Was she this anxious too?
Well, thank you.
It makes me very happy that you like it.
What's the matter, Maureen?
Did we lose your girl?
Look at her!
Doesn't good art make you guys cry?
I'm not exaggerating!
The costume alone is happy perfection!
And you stick Juju in there and it gets even more perfect somehow!
I can die happy!
Fan service is your calling!
Thanks, but pull it together.
The fact that every piece of costume fits you so well is a miracle!
Or witchcraft!
Unfortunately neither.
It's just a crap ton of staples.
Well, Mia?
Everybody's here, so you know what that means.
Of course!
Let's shoot this thing!
Never let your height hold you back!
Focus on portraits and chest-up shots!
Show no feet, have no problems!
If you want to show off your full body, take the photo from below!
Keep your height a mystery by keeping background blank!
As long as nothing in the shot reveals your proportions,
they'll think you're a skyscraper!
You're a genius, Miyako!
Awesome tips!
If you're tall and want to appear shorter,
then take photos sitting down or from overhead.
Don't be nervous about the coffin group tomorrow.
Just relax and let the angles do the work.
All right!
What a sight.
And super sketchy sight.
Dang, Shinju!
Your Soma-kun cosplay is so frickin' elite!
You dude-face has literal goals!
Miyako's like a magician with makeup!
This Soma makeup is totally different from when Gojo did it,
and both looks are so fab-o!
You fund your cosplays with your allowance, right?
Did you spend it all?
Uh-oh!
It's no problem!
I worked hard to get better grades in all the subjects I struggle with,
so my parents gave me extra money to spend!
Who's a good girl?
Adorable!
Must protect baby!
You look incredible too, Maureen.
Can we please take a quick picture together?
You read my mind!
Let's get that sick lighting upstairs!
I love how the movie explores Black Lobelia's past
and shows her grow into the character we all know and love,
but it would be a lie to say I wasn't a little distracted by how lovely Soma and Zakiya look.
I mean, I thought they were face-out-pins alone were as hot as they got,
but apparently I was like way off on that analysis because, oh my goodness,
those boys are absolutely stunning with a camera off!
Miyako, Suzuka, I can't thank you enough.
Cosplaying Black Lobelia was a dream come true.
We should be thanking you.
We were both dying to see you decked out in the costume.
Absolutely!
So thank you for indulging us.
The truth is, I was going to give up cosplay.
Sure, I enjoy it, but I figured I would have to quit someday.
Why did you think that? Did your parents say something?
No, everyone in my life is nothing but supportive and kind.
Cosplay lets me become the characters I've admired since I was a child.
It makes me truly happy.
Regardless, there's something in the back of my mind.
It's high time I let you in on a little secret.
No happiness in life can last forever.
I wondered how long I'd be allowed to continue.
I don't go to cosplay events, and I've been cosplaying alone for ages now.
I've never had the chance to talk to older cosplayers.
But since meeting you, Miyako, I've realized cosplay is a hobby for everyone.
Including adults.
No, don't make me feel ancient.
There are loads of people decades older than us that cosplay too.
I had no idea.
I know this mom who's about 40 and still cosplays the cutest idols.
How do you do, fellow kids?
Huh?
I know this one dude in his 50s who can put together a kick-butt hero cosplay.
He's loved heroes ever since he was a kid.
With most things, there's this stigma that you have to do it while you're still young.
But humans are adults for the vast majority of our lives.
And it would be a huge waste of those lives not to do what we love.
If something matters to you, then you can chase it for as long as you want.
Starting late is cool too.
Who really cares about age?
Come on.
We'll cosplay ourselves out to pasture.
Happiness is a must for survival.
A hundred percent.
Cosplay is pure joy.
Wrinkles won't make me ditch that.
I'll let you in on one more big fat grown-up secret.
Truth is, being an adult is epic.
After all that scrounging, you have real adult money to spend.
You definitely have less free time, but it's worth it.
The power of money gives you so much fun stuff to do.
But, uh, I have trouble budgeting.
So I'll wait on my paychecks.
There have been times when I thought someone stole my credit card info,
but it was actually me on a spending spree and I totally blanked out.
Why make the money if you're not gonna spend it, right?
You talk about being adults, but it sounds like you're both still kids to me.
Yeah, we suck as adults.
Whatever. Happiness is priceless.
What you said, the way you feel about Miyako and Suzuka, I get it.
I feel the same way.
I'm going to do everything in my power to make Kitakawa's dreams come true.
It's the least I can do.
It is.
Right.
It gets the Maureen's stamp of approval?
Uh, Mom's calling to check in.
Guess what? The takuyaki is a hint!
Hm? Hang on. Weird. Why didn't Akira come today?
to come today.
Aki's way too busy making props
for tomorrow to join us for Takayaki.
Show it straight, please.
Does Akira just not lick me or something?
What an awful idea!
How did you possibly come up with such a peculiar motion?
When I came back from the bathroom at karaoke,
I saw her chatting with you guys and being totally chill.
She didn't make a peep when I was there,
so I assumed I was the problem.
Was I right?
Ah, it's funny you mention that because she actually...
Who cares if someone hates you?
You can't change your personality,
so just accept it.
There's nothing funny about that!
I'm not the type to let it bug me.
I like pretty much everything and everyone.
We're super sorry, Mari.
所以是不是
緊 grupp的
快喜
淋
是
The look for it on the unfortunate smile
Last night is different from one another
You feel we feel we need to give you to
The message has التي to you
Big shipping and new curriculum
The smile of my heart
Them at value
Pony
カワイイガイワイトキメキ感じて 君からの変身まで カワイイガイワイ胸も高鳴る 雨変わるよ 君と変わるよ
カワイイガイワイ